John N. Rowe III papers, Inclusive: 1510-1989, undated, Bulk: 1830-1880
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Early Texas Documents, 1801-1989, undated; 2
  - Legal, 1801-1924, undated; 2
    - Legal: Horrib, William, 1853 October (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Horton, A. C., William S. Day, Emeline Day, William W. Chochrane, 1860 January 3 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Hosner, R. K., Samuel Maas, 1839 December 26 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Hotchkiss, A., David Gistman, 1835 December 14 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Hotchkiss, Archibald, 1834 June 23 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Hotchkiss, Archibald, Benjamin Hawkins, “Contract Splitting Profits of Texas Land Sold to Creek Indian Nation”, 1835 May 2 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Hotchkiss, Archibald, Samuel Thompson, 1835 July (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Hotchkiss, William, Thomas Robinson, 1853 December 1 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Houston East & West Texas Railway Company, 1877 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Houton, Samuel Maas, 1847 December 22 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Howan, Frederick D., 1844, 1845 August, October (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Howard, F. C., 1848 May (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Howard, F. D. and James P. Collins, 1844 August (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Howard, 1844 August (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Howard, James, Alfred M. Horton, 1832 August 2 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Howard, Talefurrs, 1850 February (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Howe, H. H., William McFarland, undated (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Howth, W. E., Swensen & Swisher, 1856 July 15 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Hubbard, Zadock, John Warren, Jacob G. Remick, Oscar Farish, 1845 November 11 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Hubbard, Zadock, Richardson and Lewis, 1845 November 17 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Hubbell, Henry, A. B. Wildman, N. D. Labadie, 1851 July 9 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Huckins, James, John L. Darrugh and Ellen Georgiana Charlton Harris, 1842 May 3 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Hudleson, C., 1845 May (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Hudson, William M., Barque Lowell, 1847 March 13 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Hughes, A. M. & Mary G., William F. Crowe, 1857 August 24 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Hunner, Francis, Richard Boatright, undated (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Hunt, Eleazer P., Memucan Hunt, James A. Miller, John W. Bennett, 1846 January 31 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Hunt, Eleazer P., John S. Jones, 1846 January 30 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Legal: Hunt, Eleazer P., Charles S. Beisner, 1854 June 6 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Legal: Hunt, E. P., 1855 May 4 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Legal: Hunt, E. P., Jonathan Brock, John Burdgess, William Meguire, 1857 July 8 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Legal: Hunt, Memucan, 1839 May 27 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Legal: Hunt, Memucan, A. C. Hinton, Lucien G. Bachelor, 1845 April 26 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Legal: Hunter, Jacob M., Charles G. Bryant, 1841 December 31 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Legal: Hurd, James G., F. Howard, J. L. Jones, Steamship Republic, 1844 August 9 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Legal: Hurd, William L., Stewart Newell, 1840 July 7 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Hurdle, Lewis J., 1840 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Hurdy, John M., Charles Mariner, 1842 August 20 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Hussey, Michael, Nicholas Lidstone, 1860 November 27 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Hyde, N. C., 1860 July (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Illies, John H., John H. Burnett, 1849 September 25 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Illies, Malvina Cecilie, John H. Burnett, 1849 September 25 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Ingraham, George F., 1912 November 5 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Ives, Charles, William F. Crow, 1848 September 15 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Ives, Sarah H., Augustus F. Ives, 1848 May 29 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Jackson, William, John S. Sydnor and Robert Moore, 1844 November (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Legal: James, A. F., David Davis, 1841 May 7 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Legal: James, A. F., Enoch Everitt, Frederick W. Muller, Pryor Bryan, John A. Little, 1847 February 5 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Legal: James, Alfred F., Frederick W. Muller, 1847 May 5 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Legal: James, A. F., John S. Syndor, Butterworth & Wife, Bennett & Hurst, 1853 August 17 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Legal: James, Alfred F., A. W. Caufield, 1853 November 14 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Legal: James, John S., Edward Hamrick, 1858 January 3 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Jeannotat, Francis H. and Alfred Jeannotat, 1847 October (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Jeffers, John E., Wesley W. Pace, Robert D. Johnson, 1840 October 28 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Jeffrey, J. E., W. W. Pacie, 1839 November 30 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Jockulsch, John M., John Royal, Robert Mills, J. P. Mallin, George M. Tuggle, 1855 August 21 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Jockusch, John W. and Elisa Moller, Richard Hennesy, 1848 May 9 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Johnson, A. J., H. L. Johnson, William M. Haslett & Lucinda Haslett, 1882 March 4 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Johnson, Chauncey, William Lindsey, 1867 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Johnson, Lucy, Hugh McLeod, Gilbert Winnie, Robert D. Johnson, Thomas Chubb, Henry Hubbell, Owen D. Johnson, 1851 January 4 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Johnson, Lucy, Thomas Chubb, Henry Hubbell, 1851 June 19 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Johnson, Lucy, Thomas Chubb, 1851 October 7 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Johnson, Lucy, Thomas Chubb, 1857 June 3 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Johnson, Lucy, Thomas Chubb, 1851 June 6 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Johnson, Lucy, Thomas Chubb, Henry Hubbard, James Wigley, 1851 June 17 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Johnson, Robert D., Isaac White, 1852 December 9 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Johnson, Thomas, Harrison & Wood, 1847 May 17 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Johnston, Garrisson, 1853 October (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Jones, Churchill, C. H. Sterns, 1853 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Jones, Henry B., Mary E. Rowe, 1856 May 15 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Jones, John, John Delesdenier, Joseph A. Perkins, 1846 Fall (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Jones, John M., Oscar Farish, 1859 May 7 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Jones, John S., N. H. Hill, John Delesdenier, 1849 July 2 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Jones, John S. John Lambert, 1856 February 28 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Jones, John S., Benjamin Burris, 1856 May 30 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - J Legal: Jones, Levi, William M. Cook, 1844 May 17 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Jones, Levi, Edward Hall, 1846 August 1 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Jones, Levi & Lucy, David S. Kelsey, Gail Borden, Jr., John S. Jones, 1844 March 6 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Jones, Levi, James Cook, 1838 May 18 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Jones, Levi, Michael B. Menard, Edward Hall, 1846 July 30 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Jones, Levi, Edward Hall, Benjamin C. Franklin, 1840 October 14 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Jones, Levi, John Box, Marmaduk Harmon, Joseph B. Tull, Christopher Orr, J. W. Moore, Thomas M. Joseph, 1851 May 22 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Jones, Levi, Henry L. Kinney, Thomas F. McKinney, Daniel M. Williams, Charles Daniel, J. W. Moore, 1852 April 24 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Jones, R. P., Thomas Chubb, 1850 January 10 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Jones, R. P., Thomas Chubb, 1850 January 10 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Jones, Richard, H.B. Martin, 1849 December 24 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Jones, Richard P., Charles Frankland, 1844 April 4 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Jones, Richard Payne, Alexander McCleland, 1845 May 20 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Jones, Richard Payne and John J. Brock, 1851 June (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Jones, Richard Payne, Henry B. Martin, 1852 June 8 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Jones, Simon L., Kinney & Aubrey, 1847 May 24 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Jones, Simon L., William Ashton, Jr., 1852 July 3 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Jones, William (Jefferson), John M Paul, S. Hunter, 1834 January 29 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Karnatz, Dores, A. P. Lufkin, D. Holland, Dorah Hamann, August Hamann, T. H. Hamann, 1854 June 6 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Kellogg, Charles, William R. Baker, James A. Thompson, 1856 December 27 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Kelman, Francis A., Robert D. Johnson, Edward Hall, 1857 January 27 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Kennedy, Joseph, John H. McKae, 1838 April 13 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Keogh, M. J., James Keane, 1839 November 29 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Kerns, Ada M., Noah Kerns, 1841 August 30 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Kerr, H., Johnston & Dewberg, 1855 October (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Kimball, John P., James G. Rhodes, William H. Rhodes, and Sydnor & Hopkins, 1845 February (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Kinney, Henry L., Ephraim McLean, 1844 September 20 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Kirven, O.C., Capt. J. H. Collett, 1889 October 15 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Klahn, Hannah, James P. Nash, 1846 February 5 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Kleiber, Charles E., Galveston Appollo Club, 1845 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Knight, James, John L. Wood, 1840 May 1 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Kohl, C., 1870 October 1 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Kramer, B., 1853 December 21 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Legal: Kramer, B. (Estate of), 1854 January 6 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Legal: Krammer, Henry, Jr., Fredrich Schmidt and Henry Krammer, Sr., 1847 April (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Legal: Kuykendall, A. L., John S. Syndor, P. G. Street, 1841 August 23 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Lacy, Hamist, Palmer and Luce, and A. B. Levitt, 1855 July (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Legal: LaFond, John, 1848 May (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Lampkins, P. O., M. J. Rusk, L. H. Mabbitt, 1836 July 24 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Lang, John, Henry Bock, John Brook, William H. Rhodes, 1847 July 27 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Lang, Nicholas, circa 1800s (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Lansing, James, Alfred Coleman, 1843 May 29 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Lanthrop, J.T., 1850 December 24 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Lapsely, John W. “Sale of Lands Near Waco”, 1868 April 15 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Lashly, Arnold, 1839 November 13 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Latham, Brazilla, William McCullough, Travis McKnight, Stewart Newell, 1839 May 29 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Laughter, John, Jane Laughter, Henry Laughter, 1846 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Lawrence, Charles, 1849 September (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Legal: Lawrence, Charles, James Brock, 1849 August 16 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Lawrence, George F., Kitton Hoyt, 1840 September 18 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Legal: LaFank, P., Levi Barrow, Robert White, J. T. White and Ben Wade, 1846 September (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, Edward Hall, 1846 November 30 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, Edward Hall, 1849 June 20, 1850 January 5 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, Edward Hall, 1850 June 21 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton et. al. and, Edward Hall, 1855 June (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, Edward Hall, 1855 June 12, 1855 October 12 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Layton & Hall, 1855 June 15 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, Edward Hall, 1855 June 15 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, Edward Hall, 1858 January 19 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, Edward Hall, 1858 January 19, 1858 March 1, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, Edward Hall, 1860 December 3 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Layton, Buxton, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Lea, Nancy Sklillen, John C. Mayfield, Edwards, Peyton F., 1874 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Legal: League, Thomas M., John De Young, Samuel P. Brown, 1847 December 23 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Legal: League, Thomas J., John H. Westerlage, 1857 January 3 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Leary, James, 1842 March (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Leavitt, A. B., Harris & Lacy, Palmer & Luce, 1854 June 8 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Leavitt, A. B., Harris & Lacy, Palmer & Luce, 1855 January 5 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Lee, John and Anne, John S. Sydnor, 1855 July 12 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Le Grand, Alexander and John A. Ford, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Legal: LeGrand, Edwin P., R. Boyd, 1855 July 2 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Lender, John, 1849 November (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Lender, John H., Frederick Vornbaumen, 1854 March 8 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Leoss, Edward, David Richardson, 1852 May 18 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Levitow, Michael, James Love, Levi Jones, Peter J. Menard, Samuel M. Williams, 1842 September 15 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Lewis, A. M., McBray, Hemphill, 1846 May (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Lewis, Allen, Sam H. Woodbury, 1849 September 18 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Lewis, Allen, 1875 August (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Lewis, Archibald, Elisha A. Rhodes, 1837 December 13 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Lewis, Elmanson, Thomas Cooper, 1847 May 5 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Lewis, A. S., Robert D. Johnson, M. Deck, G. Gould DeShon, A. M. Jackson, 1842 March 1 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Lewis, Charles E., Robert H. Davis, 1852 February 10 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Lewis, Hattie K., J. W. McMahon William T. Austin, 1880 January 21 (envelope) (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Lewis, Francis D., 1839 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., Augustus Burr, 1848 July 6 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., John Warren, 1848 August 10 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., Augustus Burr, Alonso Follett, Alexander Follett, 1849 July 14 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas J. and Joseph Bates, 1849 Fall (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas J. and B. C. Jones, 1849 December (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., Augustus Burr, Alonzo Follett, Alexander Follett, Joseph Follett, John L. Hawkins, John Meyers, John Mosier, 1849 December 12 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., Augustus Burr, Alonzo Follett, Alexander Follett, Joseph Follett, John L. Hawkins, John Meyers, John Mosier, 1849 December 12 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., Augustus Burr, 1850 January 18 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., Augustus Burr, Alonzo Follett, Alexander Follett, Joseph Follett, Silas Wickson, 1850 January 26 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B. and Wife and Robert H. Wynn, 1851 November (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., Sarah Lewis, Robert Wynn, 1851 November 20 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., Augustus Barr, 1852 January 8 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., 1856 June (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Lewis, Thomas B., 1856 July 3 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Lewis, William, Robert Mills, John W. Jockusch, J. P. Walton, George W. Tuggle, 1857 March 2 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Liautaud, Antoine, Margaret Catherine Oberria—Marriage License, 1847 March 15 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Lightfoot, Jesse, 1867 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Lindsey, Benjamin, Philip Sublett, 1835 March 28 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Linn, Edward, Luciano Garcia, Jose Antonio Saucedo, Feliepe de la Garza, Estevan (Stephen) F. Austin, Rebecca Cumming, de Bastrop, John Austin, Samuel M. Williams, Caleb R. Bostic, Robert Brotherton, Samuel Chance, William Selkirk, Thomas R. Bell, Sylvania Castleman, Elizia Allen, Robert M. Elgin, “English Translation of Title and Survey of Land Grant”, 1859 July (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Linn, John J., James A. Moody, Daniel McDonald, 1845 July 29 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Lipscomb, Abner S., McMucan Hunt, 1845 March 7 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Lister, George, Joshua C. Shaw, James P. Collins, 1850 March 20 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Lister, George, John Bennett, 1851 September 15 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Locke, James H., Oscar Farish, Henry B. Martin, Edward P. Calkin, Samuel Jones, 1847 January 29 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Lockhart, Charles H., William Van Alstyne, 1847 December 6 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Lockhart, Robert, Joseph Bratton, 1852 February 16 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Logan, Robert and Robert Shumway, 1846 February (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Logan, William M., Samuel Whiting, James W. Sumner, Sterling O. Tarpley, 1838 September 1 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Loliver, John, Sam Locke, M. B. Dewey, 1843 April (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Legal: London, Max H., 1858 October 27 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Legal: London, Meyer H. and John O. Trueheart, 1858 December (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Legal: Looney, Joseph K., James Thompson, Green DeWitt, 1831 January 24 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Lord, Samuel, Henry Hubble, 1851 December 13 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Lott, E. E., James Dale, 1858 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Louis, Francis D., David Davis, 1839 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Love, James, Al Horn, R. Edmunds, 1845 April 25 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Love, James, Levi Jones, Samuel M. Williams, M. B. Menard, George W. L. Bond, 1845 August 25 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Love, James & Henry B. Martin, Julius Kaufman, E. Allen, M. G. Hale, P. Edmunds, D. H. Grove, Old Union Bank of Louisiana, 1855 November 8 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Low, Samuel, Henry Hubbell, Lorenzo Sherwood, 1851 June 9 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Lowe & Thurmond-General Land Office, 1886 April 28 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Lowery, John and Thompson & Drew, 1848 December (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Lund, Anderson, 1842 September (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Lund, Anderson, 1843 July (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Lusk, Samuel, Edward Bailey, William W. Loyd, 1839 February 1 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Lynch & Co., Henry Hubbell, P. G. Phipps, 1848 May 10 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Lynch, E. O., 1847 January 22 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Lynch, James, Amos Gates, 1842 August 25 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Lynch, James, Amos Gates, William Deaver, Hannah Byrd, 1841 October 6 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Lynn, A. T., John H. Illies, 1849 March 31 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Maas, James and William Robertson, 1856 July (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Maas, Samuel, 1852 October (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Maas, Samuel, Benjamin S. Parsons, 1855 April 30 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Maas, Samuel, Parsons, J. Page, 1855 May 15 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Maas, Samuel, William Icet, 1856 June 12, 1856 May 5 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Mack, Henry, Letty Mack, 1908, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Maggitt, John H. and J. L. Bostick, 1851 June (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Magill, J. H., 1850 July (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Maight, James S., 1846 April 6 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Mann, Williams, Redmond, L. L. Jones, H. L. Kinney, William P. Aubrey, 1847 May 21 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Marian, Elizabeth and H. A. Cobb, 1850 October (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Marsh, Shubael, John P. Coles, 1837 September 25 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Marshal, E. J., 1871 July 26 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Marshall, John R., Andrew B. James, Augustus Hotchkiss, William A. Bennett, 1848 February 24 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Marshall & James, Hotchkiss & Bennett, 1848 November 24 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Martin, Henry B., Ebenezer B. Nichols, 1853 June 14 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Martin, James R., 1846 March (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Martin, Moses T., Robert J. Clow, Asa Hoxey, 1839 March (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Martin, Peter, undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Martin, Samuel H., Thomas B. Stephenson, James H. Bostick, 1839 May 4 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Martin, Wyly, Randal Jameson, 1846 September 10 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Mast, Milton, Rape and Swift, Owens, 1882 September 21 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Mathias, Juan, Lorenzo Sherwood, William H. Goddard, 1855 October 27 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Mason, William and Joseph W. Mason (Slave Female), 1859 October (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Maume, M. W., 1862 August 4 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Maume, Stephen W. and John S. Sydnor, 1850 May (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Maume, William & Wife, James P. Nash, 1866 July 18 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Maume, William, undated (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Mayfield, James L., Edward Hall, Layton & Co., 1845 May 19 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Maynard, William J., George N. Nash, 1849 April 14 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Legal: McClanahan, John C., Robert Mills, John Adams, James H. McMillian, 1845 February 24 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Legal: McCheaster, Hiram B. and William F. Wilson, 1845 October (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Legal: McCleland, Alexander, Jacob & Mary Schroder, 1846 January (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Legal: McCormick, Mrs., 1882 June (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Legal: McCown, Joshua W., James W. McCown, George Butler, 1854 June 12 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Legal: McCullough, William H., 1850 March (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Legal: McCullough, William H., William M. Cook, 1850 April 22 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Legal: McCullough, William H. and John McCullough, 1841 September (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Legal: McDonald, Bernard M., Isaac Kean, Robert W. Rayne, 1848 May 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Legal: McDonald, B., H. King, 1846 October 5 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Legal: McDonald, B., 1846 October 20 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Legal: McDowell, Robert, Robert Mills, A. S. Johnston, John Dewberry, 1856 December (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Legal: McDowell, Mills & Co., R. & D. G. Mills, Mr. Johnstone, 1851 February 7 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Legal: McGill, J. H., 1857 June (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Legal: McHenry, Lydia Ann and Robert Choppell, 1846 July (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Legal: McHenry, L. A., 1846 December 24 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Legal: McIver & Batte, Attorneys and Land Agents, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Legal: McKay, Joseph S., 1845 May 28 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Legal: McKee, Francis V., 1845 February 4 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Legal: McKinney, Thomas F., Jonas Butler and Henry B. Martin, 1850 June (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Legal: McKinney, Thomas F., Samuel M. Williams, Levi Jones, Thomas Green, 1852 March 5 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Legal: McKinney, Thomas F., Samuel M. Williams, Henry H. Williams, Jonas Butler, Levi Jones, 1850 February 6 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Legal: McKissack, W. H., Ralph Graves, 1869 November 9 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Legal: McLaughlin, Philip, Nathan, Taylor and Robert D. Johnson, 1840 October (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Legal: McLaughlin, P., undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Legal: McLeod, Hugh, Samuel M. Williams, John Borden, Henry and Mary G. Austin, 1853 October 29 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Legal: McLeod, Hugh, W. D. C. Hall, Benjamin C. Johnson, 1857 July 17 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Legal: McMullen, J. H., 1853 September 26 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Legal: McMullen, John, Robert Stevenson, 1841 September 7 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Legal: McWilliams, J. H., 1853 December (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Mead, William F., Sloop Champion, 1840 February 10 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Medrova, Jose Maria (Abstract of Title), 1849 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Melville, Harrison & Stewart, 1856 June 4 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Menard, Medard, Susan Leclare, 1838 November 1 (Box 22, Folder 34)